We're continuing now with the Traveling Step. All of these variations has a little bit of a, of a traveling to two sides.
Traveling front to back and traveling to the side, adding in the Knee Sweep. So we begin, drawing all the attention to your right side and we walk up, and we sweep the left knee and we walk back, sweep the right knee.
Now we walk to the right, look right, sweep the left knee.
Walk back, sweep the right knee.
Come back up, sweep the right.
Walk back, three steps, sweep.
Walk, sweep.
Sweep.
Walking back up forward, sweep.
Walk back, sweep.
Walk up, sweep.
Sweep.
Walk to the right, look right, look forward, sweep and sweep.
Walking back forward, easy walk, relaxed, continuing to breath deeply as you sweep that leg across, and sweep.
And walking back, last one, ahh!
Traveling Walk Knee Sweep.